Back we are in our burger project,
Wracamy do naszego projektu burger, czas
time to add some routing to it and use the things we learned in the last course module in a real react
na dodanie do niego routingu i wykorzystanie rzeczy, ktrych nauczylimy si w ostatnim module kursu
application.
w prawdziwej aplikacji reagujcej.
Now definitely feel free to jump ahead from time to time, puase the video and implement some feature
Teraz z pewnoci odskocz od czasu do czasu, pu wideo i zaimplementuj jak
I'm about to show you to practice using the router.
funkcj, ktr poka ci, aby wiczy korzystanie z routera.
I want to start by adding a page which allows us to actually check our burger out. Right now, checkout
Chc zacz od dodania strony, ktra pozwala nam faktycznie sprawdzi nasz burger. Teraz, kasy wyglda tak, dodajemy skadnik, klikamy
looks like this,
w
we add an ingredient, we click order now we click continue and then we already send a request to the
porzdek, teraz klikamy dalej, a nastpnie wysyamy danie do zaplecza, aby
backend to submit that burger and to save it there.
przesa tego burgera i zapisa go tam.
Now I'd like to change this so that I have to actually enter some information in a checkout form
Teraz chciabym to zmieni, abym faktycznie wprowadzi pewne informacje w formularzu
before we really save the burger.
zamwienia, zanim naprawd uratujemy burgera.
So this should be the first other page I want to have, a checkout page.
To powinna by pierwsza druga strona, ktr chc mie, strona kasy.
I also have a link here at the top which might allow us to navigate there, though we'll probably replace
Mam te link na grze, ktry moe nam pomc w nawigacji, ale prawdopodobnie zastpimy to
this throughout this module with my orders page because that makes more sense.
w tym module moj stron zamwie, poniewa ma to wicej sensu.
But let's start with the checkout component and let's start with building that in the next lecture.
Ale zacznijmy od komponentu kasy i zacznijmy od zbudowania tego na nastpnym wykadzie.
Definitely feel free to jump ahead and build it on your own but also feel free to do it together with
Zdecydowanie zachcamy do przeskakiwania do przodu i samodzielnego budowania, ale moesz take zrobi
me because obviously there are a lot of different ways of creating checkout component and creating
to razem ze mn, poniewa oczywicie istnieje wiele rnych sposobw tworzenia komponentu kasowego, a samo utworzenie
the component itself is a nice practice but not really related to routing.
komponentu jest przyjemn praktyk, ale nie jest tak naprawd zwizane z routingiem .
See you in the next lecture.
Do zobaczenia na nastpnym wykadzie.